Guide to the Living Stage records 1965-2001
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
Living Stage records
1965-2001
C0277
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
48.0 linear feet (106 boxes)
The Living Stage records include pieces related to the traveling theater company, which was founded by Robert Alexander, between 1965 and 2001.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Arena Stage in 2000.
Scope and Content
The Living Stage records consist of materials spanning the length of that organization's history from about 1965, when the Living Stage was known as the Children's Theatre, to 2001. Included in the records are administrative files including financial papers, grant requests and applications, printed pieces, and correspondence and more creative materials including workshop reports and scripts, audiovisual files on reel-to-reel tapes, and photographic materials.
Series 1: Administrative and Financial Files (1965-2000) includes documents relating to the day to day running of the Living Stage Theatre Company as well as programming, project planning, financials, budgets, grants, press releases and printed documents. It is divided further into 4 subseries. Subseries 1.1 Policies, Planning, and Development includes the administrative files of the Living Stage including season summaries by date, long range plans, meeting minutes, and Community Service Project information. Subseries 1.2 Grants and Foundations contains all materials related to grant requests, endowments (including the National Endowment for the Arts), and donations made by both large charitable organizations and private donors. Subseries 1.3 Financials and Correspondence includes budget materials, expense reports, and benefit information, as well as correspondence between members of the LSTC, memos, and fan mail (called "love letters") from schools and other workshop sites. Subseries 1.4 Public Relations and Printed Pieces consist of various publications made by the Living Stage such as their newsletters and advertisements, as well as transcripts of speeches made by LSTC executives and press releases promoting the Living Stage.
Series 2: Artistic and Workshop Files (1966-2001), which is split into 3 subseries, contains the creative aspects of the Living Stage, including details about residencies and the personnel of the Company, as well as workshop reports, scripts, and "Jams". Subseries 2.1 Residency and Personnel Files contains all documents related to the people of the Living Stage, including casting information and details about out of state residencies (including those in Stockholm, Boston, Pittsburgh, New York and others). Subseries 2.2 Production Reports and Workshops encompasses the output of the Living Stage Theatre Company in the form of workshops, which are series of performances put on at schools, museums, and communities, and the production reports which sought to analyze audience reception of and reaction to these performances. Look to the "Baltimore Incident" for an excellent example of how contentious and revolutionary the Living Stage's performances were. Subseries 2.3 Production Files and Scripts, while small, contains items related to the Living Stage's "Jams" including scripts, research, and other assorted play files.
Series 3: Audiovisual Materials (1967-1998) includes all photos, negatives, and film of the Living Stage or their productions. It is divided into three subseries. Subseries 3.1 Photographic Materials includes various photos and negatives showing the cast of the Living Stage at various times as well as production stills. Unfortunately, the majority of these are undated or have little in the way of description. Subseries 3.2 Reel to Reel Materials includes tapings of various workshops and productions mostly from the 1970s and 1980s. Subseries 3.3 Cassete and VHS tapes contains cassette, VHS, Betamax, and U-matic tapes either used by the Living Stage for performances or made by/about the Living Stage.
Historical Information
The Living Stage Theatre Company began in 1966 as a venture of the Arena Stage and Robert Alexander. Known from 1966-1968 as the Children's Theatre, the Living Stage from the beginning dedicated itself to programming with a social consciousness and a desire to effect societal change through performance. Robert Alexander was the theatre's founder and until 1995 its director. Alexander brought an adapted street and guerilla theater style to the DC area after becoming disenchanted with traditional theater's "middle-class" audience. The Living Stage provided training to actors in the art of improvisational theater through tuition free schooling during the summers, as well as through weekend long workshop training for social workers, teachers, and other professionals throughout their 9 month season. While most of the Stage's workshops were held on site at schools, museums, and prisons, the Living Stage did have its own formal space in Washington DC on 14th and T Streets NW. The Living Stage put on productions across Northern Virginia in schools, youth homes, and even prisons like the Lorton Penitentiary. Senior members of the company, like Jennifer Nelson and Oran Sandel helped to send the Living Stage across the country as well. Their efforts were largely funded through vigorous campaigning for grants and fund raising through the National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) and other private foundations. The Living Stage also received substantial financial assistance from its parent company, the Washington Drama Society, Inc.
The Living Stage performance style consisted of "The Jam", "The Performance" and "The Workshop"; a three part study that was used at most of their venues. The first part, or "Jam", consisted of actors working with their audience to "rap", make music, and "jam" through spoken or sung words accompanied by instrumentals typically provided by audience members. Then the actors moved into the "performance" itself. During the performance, the actors put on an improvised theater production directed by a senior member of the cast and assisted by one or two audience members. The "Workshop" began from there; during the workshop, the audience took over the scene, while still directed by the actors, and was encouraged to make it their own. Audiences gave their opinions and thoughts on each performance in the form of production reports that were collected by the Living Stage.
The projects that the Living Stage put on typically dealt with controversial and sensitive topics like race, economic inequality, the dangers of an overzealous American foreign policy, the atom bomb, violence, and freedom. The "Baltimore Incident" of 1971 is an excellent example of how controversial these productions could be. No matter how mixed opinions were, the Living Stage always elicited a reaction with their improvisational performances. During the 1980s the Living Stage began to reach out extensively to local initiatives like The District's Alcohol and Drug Abuse Services Administration and created their own Community Services Project in order to continue to bring theater and creativity to underserved sections of society. The Living Stage championed New Left ideals like equality and social justice throughout the Reagan years, despite some criticisms about their message being "anachronistic".
The organization began its twilight years in the first half of the 1990s as many of its founding and senior members began to take their skills elsewhere. Robert Alexander himself left in 1995 to start educating people in the art of improvisational theater full time. Jennifer Nelson, David Matthew Proctor, Ezra Knight, and others began to filter away in the 1990s to pursue their own acting goals and the Living Stage would officially close its doors in 2002.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into three series, each of which is divided into subseries.
Series 1: Administrative and Financial Files, 1965-2000 (Boxes 1-56)
Series 2: Artistic and Workshop Files, 1966-2001 (Boxes 57-85)
Series 3: Audiovisual Materials, 1967-1998 (Boxes 86-106)
Technical Requirements
The Special Collections Research Center does not have the equipment necessary to watch Betacam, U-matic, reel-to-reel film and audio tapes contained in Series 3. Additional time and money may be required to digitize this material for access.
Related Material
The Special Collections and Research Center holds several collections of personal papers of individuals involved with the Living Stage Theater Company collection Arena Stage, including the Zelda Fichandler papers, the Thomas Fichandler papers, and the Ken Kitch papers, as well as the Arena Stage collection and many other theater collections.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
Washington (D.C.)
Subjects:
Acting.; People with mental disabilities--Services for--United States.; Performance art--Photographs.; Public schools--Virginia.; Radicalism--United States--History--20th century.; Students--Photographs.; Theater--United States--History--20th century.; Theater--Washington (D.C.)
Document Types:
Playscripts.; Theatre programs.
Contents List
- Series 1: Administrative and financial files, 1965-2000
  Scope and Content
  Series 1. Administrative and Financial Files (1965-2000) includes documents relating to the day to day running of the Living Stage Theatre Company as well as programming, project planning, financials, budgets, grants, press releases and printed documents. It is divided further into 4 subseries. Subseries 1.1 Policies, Planning, and Development includes the administrative files of the Living Stage including season summaries by date, long range plans, meeting minutes, and Community Service Project information. Subseries 1.2 Grants and Foundations contains all materials related to grant requests, endowments (including the National Endowment for the Arts), and donations made by both large charitable organizations and private donors. Subseries 1.3 Financials and Correspondence includes budget materials, expense reports, and benefit information, as well as correspondence between members of the LSTC, memos, and fan mail (called "love letters") from schools and other workshop sites. Subseries 1.4 Public Relations and Printed Pieces consist of various publications made by the Living Stage such as their newsletters and advertisements, as well as transcripts of speeches made by LSTC executives and press releases promoting the Living Stage.
  - Policies, planning, and development, 1967-2000
    - 25th Anniversary Committee Kick-off, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 25th Anniversary, 40th Arena, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 30th Anniversary B'Day Party, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - LS/FLOC 30th Anniversary Event: Celebrating Children's Voices, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 30th Anniversary Committee Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 30th Anniversary General Info and Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 30th Anniversary Honorary Committee, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 30th Anniversary Imagination Mural, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 30th Anniversary Kick-off - Nov 19, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 30th Anniversary Materials, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 30th Anniversary Open House, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 30th Anniversary Products, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 30th Anniversary Birthday Discussion, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A.S/L.S Internship Program w/Application, circa 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ADASA, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ADASA (2), 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - ADASA, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Folder 1 of 2
    - ADASA Redbook, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Folder 2 of 2
    - ADASA Redbook, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ADASA, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ADASA - Prevention Contract Original Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - ADASA - Prevention Contract Original Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ADASA, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - ADASA - Official Letters and Forms, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - ADASA Activities Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - ADASA Redbook, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - ADASA Invoices, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Addresses of Supporters for DOE Handicapped Program, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Admin Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Admin Handwritten Notes, circa 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Adopt a Visitor Program, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Advisory Council Misc Information, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Council, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Council Minutes (Original Copies), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Folder 1 of 3
    - Advisory Council Minutes (Original Copies), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Folder 2 of 3
    - Advisory Council Minutes (Original Copies), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Folder 3 of 3
    - Advisory Council Honorary, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Alliance for Arts Education John F. Kennedy Center, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Appendage to Theatre Games, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Archiving for Laura, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Arena Conference/Endowment Campaign, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Artistic Statement from Bob [Robert Alexander], June 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Artists Alliance for Protection, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Arts Council, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - ASDSA - Regular Monthly Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ASSITEJ, 1968-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ASSITEJ, 1968-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Associate's Event, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Auction Program - Original Art, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bi-Weekly Reports (P.R. and Residencies), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Board, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Board Book, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Board Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Board Committee Meeting, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Board Committee Meeting Information, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Board Committee Meeting Information, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Board Committee Minutes and Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Board Committee Notes, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Board Development Working Group, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Board Info and Planning, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Board Meetings, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Board Meetings, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Board Meetings, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees and Advisors List, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Bob's [Robert Alexander] Paper on Self, circa 1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Bob's [Robert Alexander] Vita - Long, Post 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Bob's Bio, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Book Reviews, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Program, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Cardoza Teacher's Training Program, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Children's Caravan, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Children First - Current, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Childrenfest, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Children's Theatre Misc Notes, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Children's Theatre Program, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Children's Theatre Programs (Summer Festival), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Children's Theatre Program, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - CI Adds National Leadership Fellow to Living Stage's Honors, August 7, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Clean-up and Misc Projects, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Committee Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Living Stage Info Packet, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Communications Partnership Team, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Communications Planning, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Communications Team, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Community Partnership Team, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Community Relations Resumes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Community Services Project, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Community Services Project Redbooks, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Community Services Redbooks, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Community Service Program SSN, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Community Service Project (CSP) - Petty Cash Reports, CSP Reconciliations, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Community Services Redbooks, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Company Members Bios, circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Company Picnic, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Conflict Resolution Sheet, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Support Letters for High Risk Youth, April 1, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Corporate Luncheon, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Seminar, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Council Meeting Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - CSAP Activities, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - CSAP Application, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - CSAP Conference, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - CSP, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - CSP, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - CSP, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - CSP - General Information, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - CSP - Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - CTNI, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Alliance Arts Marketing Roundtable, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Curriculum Consultants, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - DC Artworks, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - DC Artworks SYEP, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - DC Coalition for Youth Info Packets, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - December Programming and Calendars, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Descriptions of Living Stage/Papers, etc, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Development, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Development, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Development Packet, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - DOE Model Curriculum Final Report, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - DOE Model Demonstration Project Community Involvement, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Extension of Living Stage - Tom Fichandler, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Fact Sheet, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Fact Sheets and Info, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax - Proposals, Agreements, Love Letters, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Fall Fact Sheets for Richard, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Fall Workshop Calendar Listing and P.S.A., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Family Planning Conference, October 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Fedapt Participants Forum, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Finding a New Space Crisis and PR, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - First Rehearsal Coffee Meet, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Floor Renovation and Maintenance Plans, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - General Information, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Going National Info, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Hasbro, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Hasbro (Children First Year 3), 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Health and Human Services Contract, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Hew End of the Year Report, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - HHS Georgetown - Community Empowerment Project, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - High Risk Youth Prevention Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - History of the Living Stage Original, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Howard Release/ Mental Health, October 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - I.H.A.D, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Imagine the Difference Natl. Conference, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Improv Theatre for the Classroom Redbook, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - In Service Teacher Training Program, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - In Service Teacher Training Program, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Junior League, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Juvenile Legislation Proposal, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - KOBA, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Landmarks of Living Stage, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Late Summer Workshop Fliers, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Living Stage School, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Living Stage School/Actor's Training Program, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Plan, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Long Range Planning, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Long Wharf Theatre, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Lovers Membership, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Major Programs Paper, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Management Goals, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Marketing Misc - Laura, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Notes, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Memos In, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Memos Out, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Mental Health, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Season Info, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Mission Statement, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Mission Statement, circa 1980s (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Moscow-DC Capitol Citizen's Exchange, March 13, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Museum of American Art, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - National Newspaper Index and General Productions Index, circa 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Newspapers Regarding Social Issues, circa 1960s and 1970s (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Notes on In-Service Teacher Training Program, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Opening of 20th Anniversary Season, December 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Orthopedic Continuation Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - OSAP - Concept Paper for Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - OSAP - Conference Grant Proposal, January 31, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - OSAP - Conference Support and Letters, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - OSAP - High Risk - Budget and Fact Sheets, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - OSAP - Budget Conference, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - OSAP Budget - Teen Moms, 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Parents and Children Packets and Pamphlets, circa 1990s (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Part IV Program Narrative, circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - PBS, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - PBS Film, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - PBS Film, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Peers and Teen Mothers Redbooks, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Performance Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Personnel for Brown Bag, circa 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Personnel Situation, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Planning and Annual Reports, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Princess Grace Foundation Proposal, March 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Production and Staff Meeting Notes, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Production and Staff Meeting Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Professional Theatre for Young Magazine, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Program Progress Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Programs, R. Alexander, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Programs, R. Alexander, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Proposal of Program for Handicapped Children, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Proposal to National Black Child Development Institution, March 20, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Proposal to the County of Fairfax, Department of Community Action, December 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Public Welfare Annual Report, June 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Redbook, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Redbook, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Renovation Analysis Survey, March 2, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Revamped Rubella, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)